A Guide to the Davis & Associates Architectural Drawing Collection, 1925-1985 (bulk, 1954-1985)
Special Collections, Carrier Library, James Madison University
Special Collections, James Madison University
Davis & Associates Architectural Drawing Collection, 1925-1985 (bulk 1954-1985)
Special Collections, James Madison University
5034
2 flat files, 44 rolled storage boxes (43" x 6" x 6"), and 1 flat storage box; 28.5 linear feet
The Davis & Associates Collection consists of approximately 9,580 architectural drawings and project records pertaining to the design and construction of structures for James Madison University and other buildings located in Harrisonburg, as well as Rockingham, Augusta, Shenandoah, and Page Counties. The architects D'Earcy P. Davis Jr. and Clyde E. McClintock completed these drawings between 1954 and 1985.
D'Earcy P. Davis, Jr., Clyde E. McClintock
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access to currently occupied government buildings requires written permission from the occupying agency; all others have no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Massanutten Regional Library, March 2, 2012.
Biographical Information
Davis and Associates, AIA, was founded in 1955 in Harrisonburg, Virginia. At the time, the firm's founder, D'Earcy P. Davis Jr., was working for Nielsen Construction Company. Before Davis retired in 1985, the firm had grown to provide architectural services for over thirty counties and cities in Virginia and West Virginia. They also completed work for a number of educational institutions, including James Madison University, Bridgewater College, Eastern Mennonite University, and Blue Ridge Community College. Throughout the years, the firm completed work for a number of prominent members of the community, including Governor Mark O. Hatfield, Fred Funkhouser, and Irving Ney. Clyde E. McClintock took over the firm in 1985, and remained as its head until 2003, when he also retired. Both Davis and McClintlock were members emeritus of the American Institute of Architecture.
D'Earcy Davis Jr. was born in 1917 and went on to earn a degree in structural engineering from Virginia Polytechnic Institute in 1940. He moved to Harrisonburg with his wife Frances to work for Nielsen Construction and architect Clarence Wenger. D'Earcy took his architecture-licensing exam at the University of Virginia in 1943. He continued to work for Nielsen Construction until 1955, at which point he left to found Davis and Associates. He remained as the leader of that firm for thirty years until he retired in 1985. In retirement, Davis served as president of the Rockingham Development Corporation from 1988 until his death in 1990.
Clyde McClintock was born in 1929 in Maidens, Virginia. He graduated from the University of Virginia's School of Architecture in 1951 and moved to Harrisonburg with his wife Eleanor to join Davis and Associates in 1961. After his retirement in 2003, he served on various community boards until his death in 2012.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of 9,580 sheets of records from approximately 695 different projects. The materials relate to the design and construction of a number of buildings in Harrisonburg and the surrounding areas, from 1954-1985. The types of structures represented include schools, public buildings, private residences, and businesses. The collection consists primarily of original pencil drawings on paper and vellum, sketches in a variety of media on tracing paper, and diazo and sepia diazo prints on vellum, paper, and drafting film (Mylar or frosted polyester). Several blueprints are also included, as are a few "stickybacks." This collection consists of seven series: James Madison University, Harrisonburg, Rockingham County, Augusta County, Page County, Shenandoah County, and Photographs.
Series I, James Madison University, includes approximately 1,200 sheets of architectural drawings, sketches, and other documents regarding original designs for James Madison University, as well as structures the university acquired after their construction. Notable projects include Rockingham Memorial Hospital, the School of Education's Memorial Hall (formerly Harrisonburg High School), and the JMU football stadium. This series is arranged in roughly the order in which it was received.
Series II, Harrisonburg, includes approximately 4,000 sheets of architectural drawings, sketches, and other material related to the planning and execution of designs for numerous structures in the city of Harrisonburg. Notable projects include the Rockingham National Bank, the housing projects at Franklin Heights and Harrison Heights, and several buildings for Eastern Mennonite University. This series is arranged in roughly the order in which it was received.
Series III, Rockingham County, consists of approximately 1,500 sheets of architectural drawings and other project records related to the design of buildings in Rockingham County. Numerous plans for Bridgewater College are included. Other notable projects include the Dayton Mennonite Church, Metro Pants Manufacturing Center in Bridgewater, and many buildings for Rockingham County Public Schools, such as Spotswood High School and Massanutten Vocational Technical Center. This series is arranged in roughly the order in which it was received.
Series IV, Augusta County, includes approximately 1,200 sheets of architectural drawings and records for projects in Augusta County. Major projects include an addition to Dawbarn Division, W. R. Grace & Co; Western State Hospital; and an office building for Degesch America, Inc. This series is arranged in roughly the order in which it was received.
Series V, Page County, includes approximately 65 sheets of architectural drawings and project records for contracts in Page County. Notable structures include Leggett's Department Store and several schools for Page County Public Schools, including Luray High School and Page County High School. This series is arranged in roughly the order in which it was received.
Series VI, Shenandoah County, includes approximately 850 sheets of architectural drawings and project records for buildings in Shenandoah County. Notable projects include additions to Shenvallee Lodge, Shenandoah County Memorial Hospital, and a remodeling of the Bushong House at the New Market Civil War Battlefield Memorial. This series is arranged in roughly the order in which it was received.
Series VII, Photographs, consists of various photographs relating to projects completed by Davis & Associates. They were taken in Harrisonburg, Rockingham County, Augusta County, and Shenandoah County. Some are photographs of the construction process; others are photographs of the site or the finished project. Notable photographs include two aerial photographs of Augusta County, Grace Memorial Church in Shenandoah County, and the Municipal Building in downtown Harrisonburg. This series is arranged by location.
Arrangement
Items within each series are arranged in the order in which they were received, and the materials are grouped by project as much as possible.
The collection is arranged in seven series:
I: James Madison University
II: Harrisonburg
III: Rockingham County
IV: Augusta County
V: Page County
VI: Shenandoah County
VII: Photographs
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Bibliography
"Clyde E. McClintock." Kyger Funeral Homes and Crematory, http://www.kygers.com/current-obituaries-topmenu-38/75-february-2012/1457-clyde-e-mcclintock (accessed June 28, 2012).
Davis, D'Earcy P., Jr. "Application for Membership to the American Institute of Architects." American Institute of Architects, 1957.
Gane, John F., and George S. Koyl, ed. American Architects Directory, Third Edition. New York: R. R. Bowker Co, 1970.
Harrisonburg City Directory. Harrisonburg, VA: R. L. Polk & Co, 1952-2004.
Lowell, Waverly B., and Tawny Ryan Nelb. Architectural Records: Managing Design and Construction Records. Chicago: Society of American Archivists, 2006.
"Newsmakers-Manufacturing." The Washington Post, October 26, 1981, Business section.
Pezzoni, J. Daniel. "National Register of Historic Places Registration Form for Harrisonburg Downtown Historic District." Department of Historic Resources, 2004.
Price, Lois Alcott. Line, Shade, and Shadow: The Fabrication and Preservation of Architectural Drawings. Newcastle, DE: Oak Knoll Press, 2010.
Contents List
- James Madison University
  - Remodeling & Alterations to Keezell Building, 2 Sheets (Folder 1)
  - School of Education, 1 Sheet (Folder 1)
  - Renovation of Ashby Hall and Auditorium Addition, 1973, 6 Sheets (Folder 1)
    Comm. #7128
  - Seating for Outdoor Athletic Facilities, 1974, 1 Sheet (Folder 1)
    Comm. #7417
  - Related to Madison Maury, 1969, 2 Sheets (Folder 1)
    Comm. #6919
  - Renovation of Varner House, 1 Sheet (Folder 1)
  - Renovation of Johnston Hall, 2 Sheets (Folder 1)
  - Renovation of Burruss Hall, 6 Sheets (Folder 1)
  - Madison College Site Plans, 1974, 3 Sheets (Folder 1)
  - Hospital Sketches, 1957, 3 Sheets (Folder 2)
  - Outdoor Recreation and Athletic Facilities, 1973, 24 Sheets (Folder 2)
    Comm. #7302
  - New Parking Lot for Rockingham County Hospital 1970, 2 Sheets (Folder 3)
    Comm. #7206
  - Emergency and Outpatient Facilities for the Rockingham Memorial Hospital, 1973, 71 Sheets (Folder 3-5)
    Comm. #7117
  - Gymnasium for Harrisonburg High School, 1955, 1 Sheet (Folder 6)
    Comm. #5838
  - Athletic Facilities for Harrisonburg High School, 1971, 7 Sheets (Folder 6)
    Comm. #7130
  - Harrisonburg Memorial Stadium, 1976, 3 Sheets (Folder 6)
    Comm. #7601
  - Rockingham Memorial Hospital; Partial Site Plans, 1977, 5 Sheets (Folder 6)
  - Proposed New Administrative Wing, RMH, 1977, 2 Sheets (Folder 6)
  - Proposed Lecture Room, RMH, 1977, 1 Sheet (Folder 6)
  - Topographic Survey for Rockingham Memorial Hospital, 1 Sheet (Folder 6)
  - Music Dept. 1974, 6 Sheets (Folder 6)
    Comm. #7421
  - School of Education Proposed Parking Lot Grading, 1980, 2 Sheets (Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous Harrisonburg High School Athletic Facility sheets/drawings, 25 Sheets (Folder 6-7)
  - A Stadium for Madison College 1974, 16 Sheets (Folder 8-9)
  - Locker Rooms and Supporting Facilities for the Stadium at Madison College, 1977, 37 Sheets (Folder 9-10)
    Comm. #7503
  - Rockingham Memorial Hospital; Partial Site Plans, 1977, 3 Sheets (Folder 10)
  - Topographic Survey for Rockingham Memorial Hospital, 1977, 2 Sheets (Folder 10)
  - Pediatrics Floor for Rockingham Memorial Hospital, 1968, 22 Sheets (Folder 11)
    Comm. #6725
  - Additions & Alterations to Rockingham Memorial Hospital, 1966, 93 Sheets (Folder 12-15)
    Comm. #6515
  - Madison College Centrex Harrisonburg Telephone Company, 1969, 1 Sheet (Folder 16)
    Comm. #6912
  - Athletic Field for Harrisonburg High School, 22 Sheets (Folder 16)
    Comm. #6632
  - Proposed Addition to Rockingham Memorial Hospital, 1977, 65 Sheets (Folder 17-19)
  - Completion of Seating for Outdoor Athletic & Recreational Facilities, 1976, 7 Sheets (Folder 20)
  - Maps for the Proposed Steam Generation Plant Site and Route Location Through JMU Property, 1980, 7 Sheets (Folder 20)
  - Home Economics Kitchen, 1969, 18 Sheets (Folder 21)
  - Proposed School of Education Building, 1976, 8 Sheets (Folder 21)
    Comm. #7423
  - Nurses Home & School, RMH, 1957, 47 Sheets (Folder 22)
    Comm. #5615
  - Laundry Room Revisions for Rockingham Memorial Hospital, 1977, 2 Sheets (Folder 23)
    Comm. #7709
  - Garbage Room for RMH, 1958, 3 Sheets (Folder 23)
    Comm. #5913
  - Vestibule Additions to Stairway—Rockingham Memorial Hospital, 1973, 1 Sheet (Folder 23)
  - RMH—Administrative Wing, 1973, 3 Sheets (Folder 23)
  - Elevated Pedestrian Walk for RMH, 1959, 16 Sheets (Folder 23)
    Comm. #5916
  - Harrisonburg High School Gymnasium, 1958, 21 Sheets (Folder 24)
  - RMH Additions and Alterations (4th and 5th floors), 1975, 20 Sheets (Folder 24)
    Comm. #7518
  - Completion of Seating for Football Stadium, 1980, 36 Sheets (Folder 25)
    Comm. #7730
  - Completion of Seating Phase II—Football Stadium, 1977, 7 Sheets (Folder 26)
    Comm. #7730-II
  - Outdoor Recreation and Athletic Facilities, 1973, 13 Sheets (Folder 26)
  - A Stadium for Madison College, 1974, 13 Sheets (Folder 26)
  - Athletic Foundation Facility for Football Stadium, 1982, 7 Sheets (Folder 27)
    Comm. #8109
  - Completion of Seating Phase III—Football Stadium, 13 Sheets (Folder 27)
    Comm. #7730-III
  - Miscellaneous Stadium/Seating Plans, 6 Sheets (Folder 27)
  - Fixed Seating for Keezell Hall, 1986, 1 Sheet (Folder 27)
  - Tool Building for RMH, 1958, 2 Sheets (Folder 28)
    Comm. #5904
  - Pediatrics Floor for RMH, 1968, 1 Sheet (Folder 28)
  - Addition to Rockingham Memorial Hospital, 1966, 117 Sheets (Folder 28-31)
  - Addition to Rockingham Memorial Hospital (Prelim.), 1964, 35 Sheets (Folder 32-33)
    Comm. #6408
  - Baseball Field Seating, 1978, 19 Sheets (Folder 34)
    Comm. #7817
  - School of Education, 1976, 304 Sheets (Folder 35-43)
  - Madison College Site plans, 16 Sheets (Folder 44)
    Comm. #7218
  - Renovation of Ashby Hall, 6 Sheets (Folder 44)
  - Remodeling and Alterations of Maury Hall, 1 Sheet (Folder 44)
  - RMH Additions and Alterations, 1949, 72 Sheets (Folder 45)
- Harrisonburg
  - Plan and Profile of Proposed State Highway (Cantrell Ave.), 1974, 11 Sheets (Box 1)
  - Schemes (2a, 2b) for Joe Miller Property, 3 Sheets (Box 1)
  - Alterations & Addition to Rockingham County Jail, 1968, 1 Sheet (Box 1)
  - Sketch of Sunnyside Pool, 1 Sheet (Box 1)
  - Swimming Pool for Harrisonburg Rec. Dept., 5804, 1 Sheet (Box 1)
  - Science Building for Eastern Mennonite College, 1968, 1 Sheet (Box 1)
    Comm. #6530
  - Existing Front Entrance Profile, Daily News Record, 1 Sheet (Box 1)
  - Alterations for Harrisonburg Police Dept., 2 Sheets (Box 1)
    Comm. #6536
  - Transfer Print Company for Storey of Virginia, 1976, 3 Sheets (Box 1)
    Comm. #7602
  - Stehli & Co. Inc., 3 Sheets (Box 1)
  - Alterations & Additions to West Rockingham Mutual Building, 1967, 17 Sheets (Box 1)
    Comm. #6721
  - Lay Out for Harrisonburg Property Line and Fence Erection, 1925, 1 Sheet (Box 1)
  - Production Center for Shenandoah Valley Educational Television, 1967, 5 Sheets (Box 1)
    Comm. #6630
  - Addition-Alterations to W. O. Weaver Residence, 1970, 3 Sheets (Box 1)
    Comm. #6918
  - Additions-Alterations to M. A. Layman Residence, 1970, 2 Sheets (Box 1)
    Comm. #7005
  - Proposed Addition to Virginia Mennonite Home, 1967, 1 Sheet (Box 1)
  - Physicians for Children, 1971, 1 Sheet (Box 1)
    Comm. #7109
  - Proposed Bank Sign for Rockingham Nat. Bank, 1971, 5 Sheets (Box 1)
    Comm. #7104
  - Proposed Police Department Building, 1969, 6 Sheets (Box 1)
    Comm. #6940
  - Alterations to S. B. Hoover and Co., 1972, 6 Sheets (Box 1)
    Comm. #7213
  - Harrison Heights, 1959, 50 Sheets (Box 1)
    Comm. #5902
  - Proposed Plaque for Harrisonburg Electric Commission, 1980, 1 Sheet (Box 1)
  - Conveyor Pipe Line for IMCO Container Co. of Virginia, 1962, 7 Sheets (Box 1)
    Comm. #6211
  - Rockingham Coop Farm Bureau Inc. 1957, 1 Sheet (Box 1)
  - Remodeling of the Willis Building, 1961, 3 Sheets (Box 1)
    Comm. #6111
  - Garden Supply Store for Mr. & Mrs. E. H. Hudson, 1959, 10 Sheets (Box 1)
    Comm. #5918
  - Egg Grading Building for Rockingham Co-Operative Farm Bureau, 1957, 62 Sheets (Box 2)
    Comm. #5709
  - Drive-In Bank Building and Parking Lot for the National Bank, 1959, 12 Sheets (Box 2)
    Comm. #5839
  - Bethel Temple, 1963, 4 Sheets (Box 2)
  - Walkway Enclosure for W.S.V.A., 1970, 1 Sheet (Box 2)
    Comm. #7036
  - Proposed Fire Station, 1926, 48 Sheets (Box 3)
    Comm. #6826
  - Rockingham National Bank, 1961, 28 Sheets (Box 3)
    Comm. #6001
  - Addition of New Toilet to Valley Bowling Center Inc., 1959, 1 Sheet (Box 3)
  - Computer Center for Rockingham National Bank, 1972, 170 Sheets (Box 3)
  - Proposed Addition to Clark & Bradshaw Law Offices, 1968, 1 Sheet (Box 3)
    Comm. #6837
  - Topography and Utility Map, Harrisonburg Redevelopment & Housing Project/Authority, 1958, 2 Sheets (Box 4)
  - Sign Details and Location, The National Bank Drive-In Branch, 1959, 4 Sheets (Box 4)
  - Residence for Mr. & Mrs. W. F. Acker, 1958, 2 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #5829
  - Rewiring the National Bank Building, 1957, 6 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #5705
  - Board of Directors Room for the National Bank, 1958, 3 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #544
  - Additions & Alterations/Proposed Remodeling, the National Bank, 1955-1957, 10 Sheets (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous National Bank, 6 Sheets (Box 4)
  - Alterations--Residence, Mr. & Mrs. J. A. Willett III, 1958, 4 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #5815
  - Service Station for Rockingham Farm Bureau, Inc., 1954, 11 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #541
  - Coal Trestle for Rockingham Co-Op Farm Bureau, 1956, 5 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #5606
  - Miles Shoes, 1 Sheet (Box 4)
  - Swimming Pool for Harrisonburg Recreation Department, 1958, 3 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #5804
  - Mick or Mack Store, 1955, 10 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #5520
  - Rockingham County Court House/Room, 1956, 8 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #5610
  - Remodeling Assembly Hall for Courtroom for Judge Porter Graves, 1961, 3 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #6121
  - Entrance Canopy at Rockingham County Court House, 1 Sheet (Box 4)
    Comm. #5922
  - Renovations to Rockingham County Court House, 1967, 3 Sheets (Box 4)
  - New Mezzanine Floor for Office at Rockingham County Court House, 1964, 2 Sheets (Box 4)
  - Addition to Residence of Mr. & Mrs. Irving Ney, 1960, 3 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #5923
  - Proposed Nook & Book Store for Massanetta Springs, 1955, 9 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #5529
  - Proposed Dining Room & Kitchen Enlargement for Hotel at Massanetta Springs, 1954, 1 Sheet (Box 4)
  - Addition to Residence of Mr. & Mrs. Winston O. Weaver, 1957, 8 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #5836
  - New Mezzanine and Alterations to the United Virginia Bank, 1970, 8 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #7008
  - Drawing of Limited Area Along C&W RR—Rockingham Co-op and Bond Lumber, 1956, 1 Sheet (Box 4)
  - Medical Arts Building for Medical Arts Building of Rockingham, Inc., 1961, 15 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #5925
  - Low Rent Housing Projects, 1958, 39 Sheets (Box 4)
  - Rockingham Mill, 1967, 6 Sheets (Box 4)
  - Addition to Valley of Virginia Milk Producers Assoc. Inc., 1957, 27 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #5717
  - Valley Virginia Co-Op Milk Producers Assoc.--New Grade "A" Addition, 1945, 3 Sheets (Box 4)
    Comm. #4507
  - Proposed Bowling Center, Valley Bowling Center Inc., 1959, 4 Sheets (Box 4)
  - Plant and Office Building for Kawneer Company, Architectural Products Division, 1969, 203 Sheets (Box 5)
    Comm. #6922 and 6935
  - Office & Plant Expansion for Kawneer, Inc. 1980, 10 Sheets (Box 5)
    Comm. #7908
  - Office Building for Valley of Virginia Milk Producers Association, 1958, 24 Sheets (Box 6)
    Comm. #5820
  - Medical Arts Building, 1961, 21 Sheets (Box 6)
  - Map of Industrial Site, 1945, 1 Sheet (Box 6)
  - Branch Office, Old Dominion Savings & Loan 1978, 28 Sheets (Box 6)
    Comm. #7814
  - Addition and Alterations to Rockingham Public Library, 1966, 8 Sheets (Box 6)
    Comm. #6252
  - Proposed Alterations to First Presbyterian Church, 3 Sheets (Box 6)
  - Enclosed Porch for F. O. Funkhouser, 1968, 1 Sheet (Box 6)
    Comm. #6839
  - Residence Addition for Fred O. Funkhouser, 1968, 1 Sheet (Box 6)
    Comm. #6816
  - Proposed Nursing Care Center for Sunnyside Presbyterian Home, 1970, 1 Sheet (Box 6)
    Comm. #7009
  - Proposed Deck for Dr. Roberts, 7129, 1 Sheet (Box 6)
    Comm. #7129
  - Miscellaneous Massanetta Springs, 1954-1963, 6 Sheets (Box 6)
  - Lupton Cottage, 1959, 4 Sheets (Box 6)
    Comm. #5906
  - Chapel for Eastern Mennonite College, 1971, 9 Sheets (Box 6)
    Comm. #7112
  - Proposed Relocation for Drive-In Bank, First National Bank, 1969, 11 Sheets (Box 6)
  - Alterations and Studio Additions to Station WSVA TV--AM-FM, 1969, 17 Sheets (Box 6)
    Comm. #6907
  - Underground Duct Entrances for Main Office Building, Continental Telephone Co. of VA, 1968, 1 Sheet (Box 6)
    Comm. #6827
  - Alterations-Remodeling, Main Office Building for Harrisonburg Telephone Co., 1970, 5 Sheets (Box 6)
    Comm. #6924
  - Office Addition to Harrisonburg Telephone Building, 1965, 9 Sheets (Box 6)
    Comm. #6516
  - Ground Floor Alterations for the Main Office Building, Continental Telephone Company of VA, 1971, 3 Sheets (Box 6)
    Comm. #7030
  - IBM Room Alterations for Harrisonburg Telephone Company, 1965, 3 Sheets (Box 6)
    Comm. #6539
  - Additions & Alterations to the Engineering & Service Bldg. for the Continental Telephone Co., 1970, 7 Sheets (Box 6)
    Comm. #7027
  - Harrisonburg Office for the Continental Telephone Company, 1976, 8 Sheets (Box 6)
    Comm. #7612
  - Additions and Alterations to Harrisonburg Telephone Building, 1964, 12 Sheets (Box 6)
    Comm. #6324
  - Harrisonburg Telephone Company Miscellaneous, 21 Sheets (Box 6)
  - Proposed Office Expansion for Ray Carr Tires, Inc., 1982, 39 Sheets (Box 6)
    Comm. #8217
  - Corporate Office Building for Ray Carr Tires, Inc., 1983, 14 Sheets (Box 7)
    Comm. #8302
  - Office Building for Keeler, Phibbs & Co., 1981, 38 Sheets (Box 7)
    Comm. #7927
  - Sunnyside Presbyterian Home, 1957, 2 Sheets (Box 7)
    Comm. #5710
  - Book Store at Massanetta Springs Bible Conference, 1957, 4 Sheets (Box 7)
    Comm. #5721
  - Massanetta Springs, 1976, 1 Sheet (Box 7)
    Comm. #7625
  - Store for Schewels Furniture Company, 1977, 21 Sheets (Box 7)
    Comm. #7608
  - Alterations to Virginia Mennonite Home, 1975, 1 Sheet (Box 7)
    Comm. #7332
  - Studio Addition for Shenandoah Valley ETV, 1980, 24 Sheets (Box 7)
    Comm. #7837
  - Addition to Production Center for Shenandoah Valley Educational Television Corp., 1978, 19 Sheets (Box 7)
    Comm. #7620
  - Remodeling for First National Bank, 1965, 24 Sheets (Box 7)
  - First National Bank, 1956, 9 Sheets (Box 7)
  - Equipment Room Addition for the Harrisonburg Office, Continental Telephone of Virginia, 1976, 17 Sheets (Box 7)
  - Addition & Alterations to the Engineering & Service Bldg. for the Continental Telephone Co., 1971, 25 Sheets (Box 7)
  - Harrisonburg Office of the Old Dominion Savings and Loan Association, 1971, 94 Sheets (Box 8)
    Comm. #7103
  - Dining Wing Addition to the Howard Johnson's Restaurant, 19668, 18 Sheets (Box 8)
    Comm. #6688
  - A Building for Harrisonburg Loan & Thrift Corp., 1959, 30 Sheets (Box 8)
    Comm. #5919
  - Miscellaneous Harrisonburg Loan and Thrift, 1960, 26 Sheets (Box 8)
  - Harrisonburg Loan and Thrift, 1965, 2 Sheets (Box 8)
    Comm. #6524
  - Warehouse Addition to IMCO Container Company, 1979, 37 Sheets (Box 8)
    Comm. #7917
  - Office Remodeling for RNB, 1981, 5 Sheets (Box 8)
    Comm. #8118
  - Millwork for Second Floor Nurses' Station, Sunnyside Presbyterian Home, 1964, 1 Sheet (Box 8)
  - Proposed Classroom Addition to Waterman Elementary School, 1974, 3 Sheets (Box 8)
    Comm. #7415
  - Library Addition to Waterman Elementary School, 1973, 25 Sheets (Box 8)
    Comm. #7229
  - VA-14-1, Harrisonburg Revised Layout, 1959, 2 Sheets (Box 8)
  - Walker Manufacturing Plant, 1971, 3 Sheets (Box 8)
  - Classroom Addition to Keister Elementary School, 1981, 18 Sheets (Box 9)
    Comm. #8107
  - Library Addition to Spotswood Elementary School, 1 Sheet (Box 9)
    Comm. #7303
  - Classroom Addition to Spotswood Elementary School, 1981, 24 Sheets (Box 9)
    Comm. #8121
  - The Harrisonburg Electric Commission 69KV/13.2-23 KV Substation, 1976, 1 Sheet (Box 9)
  - Proposed Remodeling of Residence, Col. & Mrs. R. T. Benson, 1977, 3 Sheets (Box 9)
  - Reservoir Street Sub-Station for Harrisonburg Electric Commission, 1977, 1 Sheet (Box 9)
    Comm. #7422